# FARWA SYED

JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER

Number: +61 - 0406 - 014 - 156 Email: farwa.asyed@gmail..com Portfolio: fahz1.github.io/porfolio/

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/farwa-alisyed/

## PROFILE SUMMARY

I am a Junior Web Developer looking for new opportunities as a Front End Developer in a challenging environment.
I recently up-skilled with General Assembly's Web
Development Immersive bootcamp to brush up my skills with
Javascript, Ruby on Rails, React, Vue, Node, HTML5, CSS, and
much more!

With over 6 years experience in design and marketing, I thrive on working with people from different backgrounds and love taking on new challenges everyday.

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- HTML5, CSS/SCSS, JAVASCRIPT
- JS Libraries, REACT, VUE, NODE, jQUERY, DOM, API, REST API, RUBY ON RAILS, Bootstrap
- POSTGRSQL, MONGODB, SQL
- JWT Authentication, JEST, ENZYME,
- Knowledge of NETLIFY, HEROKU, AWS, Git
- Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign

# **SOFT SKILLS**

Excellent Communication Results Driven Adaptabiltiy Problem Solving

# **PROJECTS**

#### Foods to Forks

A recipe finder built in React using API from food2fork.com.

- Demo: https://fahz1.github.io/foods2forks
- Github: https://github.com/fahz1/foods2forks

## **Vue Music Player**

A music player with audio visualisation built using Vue.js

- Demo: vue-music-player11.herokuapp.com/#/
- Github: github.com/fahz1/vue-music-player

## Movie Booking App(Group Project)

Reelsplex (Movie Booking site) using React for front end and Rails and Postgresql for server end.

- Demo: sarita2129.github.io/movie\_booking\_client/#/home
- Github: github.com/fahz1/Movie\_booking\_server

## Tic-Tac-Toe

Classic two player TicTacToe, built with Javascript, HTML5 and CSS3.

- Demo: fahz1.github.io/project0/
- Github: github.com/fahz1/project0

# Weather Checking App

Classic two player TicTacToe, built with Javascript, HTML5 and CSS3.

- Demo: https://fahz1.github.io/react-weather-app/
- Github: https://github.com/fahz1/react-weather-app

# **EDUCATION**

# **Web Development Immersive**

General Assembly Dec 2018 - March 2019

## **Graphic & Web Design Certificate**

NICON Group of Colleges, Feb 2011 - April 2011

# **Bachelors of Science in Computer Engineering**

COMSATS University of Information Technology, (2006-2010)

## **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

# **Benefits Program Manager**

One Affiniti, Sydney | May, 2017 to November, 2018

# **B2B Marketing Executive**

CBS Interactive, Sydney | June 2015 to April, 2017

## **Graphic Designer / Marketing Assistant**

FOCUS Advertising, Designing & Advertising, Dubai, UAE | March 2013 to Feb 2014

# **Design and Marketing Executive**

IMAGE Engineering Consultants, Dubai, UAE | Oct 2010 to Jan 2013